<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<eml:eml xmlns:eml="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
         xsi:schemaLocation="eml://ecoinformatics.org/eml-2.1.1 http://rs.gbif.org/schema/eml-gbif-profile/1.1/eml.xsd"
        packageId="10.15468/dl.kyegws"  system="http://gbif.org" scope="system"
  xml:lang="en">

<dataset>
        <alternateIdentifier>0240863-220831081235567</alternateIdentifier>
    <title>GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.kyegws</title>
    <creator>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </creator>
    <metadataProvider>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>    </metadataProvider>
      <pubDate>
      2023-01-08
      </pubDate>
    <language>ENGLISH</language>
    <abstract>
        <para>A dataset containing all occurrences available in GBIF matching the query:
{
  &quot;and&quot; : [
    &quot;GadmGid is MDG&quot;,
    &quot;Geometry POLYGON((49.36929 -16.91721,49.83544 -16.88654,49.93664 -16.63814,49.99491 -16.14746,49.36929 -16.14746,49.36929 -16.91721))&quot;
  ]
}
The dataset includes records from the following constituent datasets. The full metadata for each constituent is also included in this archive:
1 records from University of Michigan Museum of Zoology, Division of Reptiles &amp; Amphibians
1 records from P herbarium - Muséum national d’histoire naturelle, Paris - Amostras Brasileiras Repatriadas - Herbário Virtual REFLORA
1 records from New combinations and typifications in Vitex (Lamiaceae) from Madagascar
1 records from Observatoire Pelagis aerial surveys 2002-2021
1 records from Thunberga gen. nov., a new genus of huntsman spiders from Madagascar (Araneae: Sparassidae: Heteropodinae)
1 records from Royal Museum of Central Africa - True Fruit Flies (Diptera, Tephritidae) of the Afrotropical Region (ENBI wp13)
1 records from Botany (UPS)
1 records from Botanical Database of Southern Africa (BODATSA): Botanical Collections
1 records from Botanical Research Institute of Texas, Philecology Herbarium
1 records from A taxonomic study of Dinapsis Waterson, 1922 from Madagascar (Hymenoptera Megalyridae, Dinapsini): crested wasps of the hirtipes species-group
1 records from Database about reference specimens for medicinal plants, in the Apocynaceae family, owned by CNARP
1 records from The molluscs collection (IM) of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
1 records from University of Vienna, Institute for Botany - Herbarium WU
1 records from Ecology and morphology of mouse lemurs (Microcebus spp.) in a hotspot of microendemism in northeastern Madagascar, with the description of a new species
1 records from University of Michigan Museum of Zoology, Division of Fishes
1 records from Gastrodia madagascariensis (Gastrodieae, Orchidaceae): from an historical designation to a description of a new species from Madagascar
1 records from Nouveautés taxonomiques et nomenclaturales dans le genre Pteris L. (Pteridaceae) à Madagascar
1 records from Collection Porifera - ZMB
2 records from RBINS DaRWIN
2 records from Universidad de Murcia, Dpto. Biología Vegetal (Botánica), Murcia: MUB-HEPATICAE
2 records from database_orthoptera
2 records from Database_lepidoptera
2 records from Review of the Madagascan Orphninae (Coleoptera: Scarabaeidae) with a revision of the genus Triodontus Westwood
2 records from Royal Belgian Institute of Natural Sciences Crustacea collection
2 records from Dryinidae of the Afrotropical region (Hymenoptera, Chrysidoidea)
2 records from Bryophyte Herbarium (H): Herbarium Generale
2 records from University of Jena, Herbarium Haussknecht - Herbarium JE
2 records from The cryptogamy collection (PC) at the Herbarium of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire Naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
2 records from A revision of Homalium sect. Odontolobus (Salicaceae) endemic to Madagascar
2 records from Revision of the Malagasy genus Trichoteleia Kieffer (Hymenoptera, Platygastroidea, Platygastridae) - Darwin Core Archives
3 records from TTU Mammals Collection
3 records from Biologiezentrum Linz
3 records from Observation.org, Nature data from around the World
3 records from Digitonthophagus Balthasar, 1959: taxonomy, systematics, and morphological phylogeny of the genus revealing an African species complex (Coleoptera: Scarabaeidae: Scarabaeinae)
3 records from KZNM-PINDIP-DIPTATEACH
3 records from Australian Museum provider for OZCAM
3 records from Database on reference specimens for medicinal plants of the Meliaceae family, conserved at the CNARP herbarium
3 records from A revision of Homalium sect. Nisa (Salicaceae) endemic to Madagascar
3 records from The fishes collection (IC) of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
3 records from Towards a Revision of the Genus Vitex (Lamiaceae) in Madagascar. II: Three New Species from the Littoral Forests
3 records from CAS Invertebrate Zoology (IZ)
3 records from EOD – eBird Observation Dataset
3 records from Herpetology Collection NRM
4 records from Mosquito Occurrence Dataset
4 records from Collection Mollusca SMF
4 records from University of Michigan Herbarium
4 records from KUBI Herpetology Collection
4 records from The Coleoptera collection (EC) of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
4 records from Dermaptera
4 records from Taxonomic revision of Stigmatomma Roger (Hymenoptera: Formicidae) in the Malagasy region
4 records from Bioversity Collecting Mission Database
4 records from A revision of the Malagasy species of Homalium sect. Blackwellia (Salicaceae)
5 records from Database_diptera
5 records from Specimen references on the Sapotaceae family held by the TAN Herbarium
5 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Mammalia
5 records from Museum of Comparative Zoology, Harvard University
5 records from Revision of the Malagasy species of Homalium sect. Eumyriantheia Warb. (Salicaceae)
5 records from Database about reference specimens for medicinal plants, in the Sapotaceae family, owned by CNARP
5 records from A revision of Malagasy species of Anochetus Mayr and Odontomachus Latreille (Hymenoptera: Formicidae).
5 records from Specimen references on the Rubiaceae family held by theTAN Herbarium
5 records from Database on reference specimens for medicinal plants of the Fabaceae family, conserved at the CNARP herbarium
6 records from Centre for Australian National Biodiversity Research (CANB) AVH data
7 records from CSIC-Real Jardín Botánico-Colección de Plantas Vasculares (MA)
7 records from database_dyctio
8 records from The ant genus Pheidole Westwood, 1839 (Hymenoptera: Formicidae) in Madagascar-taxonomic revision of the bessonii species-group
8 records from NMSA: Arthropod Collections (1900-2012)
8 records from The New York Botanical Garden Herbarium (NY)
8 records from Database on reference specimens for medicinal plants of the Euphorbiaceae family, conserved at the CNARP herbarium
8 records from A revision of Xylopia L. (Annonaceae): the species of Madagascar and the Mascarene islands
9 records from Database on reference specimens for medicinal plants of the Rubiaceae family, conserved at the CNARP herbarium
9 records from A global database for the distributions of crop wild relatives
9 records from Specimen references on the Verbenaceae family held by the TAN Herbarium
10 records from CAS Entomology (ENT)
10 records from Field Museum of Natural History (Zoology) Insect, Arachnid and Myriapod Collection
11 records from Phanerogamic Botanical Collections (S)
12 records from database_hemiptera
18 records from All herbarium specimens of grasses from Madagascar and the surrounding islands: family Poaceae, sector AFM
19 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Aves
21 records from pbzt_insect_biodiversity
24 records from CAS Botany (BOT)
27 records from tan-database
28 records from All herbarium specimens of grasses held at TAN herbarium
28 records from Research database of Madagascar grasses compiled by Maria Vorontsova
44 records from INSDC Host Organism Sequences
57 records from Meise Botanic Garden Herbarium (BR)
71 records from Database_Coleoptera_Madagascar Biodiversity Center PBZT
79 records from NMNH Extant Specimen Records (USNM, US)
82 records from Bryophyte specimens at TAN Herbarium
84 records from tef-database
85 records from iNaturalist Research-grade Observations
113 records from KwaZulu-Natal Museum-Entomology-collection
131 records from INSDC Sequences
153 records from Naturalis Biodiversity Center (NL) - Botany
205 records from Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew - Herbarium Specimens
364 records from The vascular plants collection (P) at the Herbarium of the Muséum national d&apos;Histoire Naturelle (MNHN - Paris)
633 records from International Barcode of Life project (iBOL)
760 records from UF Invertebrate Zoology
1891 records from AntWeb
3136 records from Tropicos Specimen Data</para>
    </abstract>
      <contact>
    <individualName>
          <surName>GBIF Download Service</surName>
    </individualName>
<electronicMailAddress>support@gbif.org</electronicMailAddress>      </contact>

</dataset>

<additionalMetadata>
    <metadata>
      <gbif>
        <dateStamp>2023-01-08T05:51:31Z</dateStamp>
      <citation identifier="10.15468/dl.kyegws">GBIF Occurrence Download 10.15468/dl.kyegws</citation>
              <physical>
                  <objectName>Darwin Core Archive</objectName>
                  <characterEncoding>UTF-8</characterEncoding>
                  <dataFormat>
                      <externallyDefinedFormat>
                          <formatName>Darwin Core Archive</formatName>
                      </externallyDefinedFormat>
                  </dataFormat>
                  <distribution>
                      <online>
                          <url function="download">https://api.gbif.org/v1/occurrence/download/request/0240863-220831081235567.zip</url>
                      </online>
                  </distribution>
              </physical>
      </gbif>
    </metadata>
</additionalMetadata>

</eml:eml>
